telegram-store.com 2019-11-08

# Privacy policy of the Telegram-Store.com site

Last updated date: 24.05.2018

This Privacy Policy applies to any information that Telegram-store.com (the Site) can receive from the User when visiting the Site and using the services provided by the Site. **The Site is available only to individuals who are at least 16 years old.**

## 1\. General Provisions

1.1. Your use of the Site implies full agreement with its Privacy Policy and the terms of collecting, processing and storing personal information. 

1.2. By submitting your personal data and agreeing to the collection / processing of other personal information within the Site, you understand that such actions are necessary to ensure the operation of the Site and the attached services. 

1.3. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected within the Site. When navigating through external links, the Site does not control the implementation of the Privacy Policy by third-party web resources and does not bear any responsibility for the use of your personal data by these resources. 

1.4. If you disagree with our Privacy Policy, you should immediately stop using the Site. 

## 2\. Collection of information

2.1. Personal data. 

To identify the User, we collect personal information that you indicate during the registration on the Site using the AuthGram system, namely: Your username in Telegram. At the same time, verification of the reliability of the provided information is not carried out. 

2.2. Technical data. 

Through the server logs we automatically collect technical information that becomes available when you visit the Site. This information includes: the IP address of the computer, the name of the internet provider, the type of browser, the operating system of the device, the time spent on the Site, information about activity (visited pages, clicks on the links, downloads of software products, etc.). 

2.3. Cookies. 

The site uses “cookie” technology to store profile settings and other information on the user’s side. When you visit the Site on your computer are recorded small pieces of data that will be used to automatically load of profile and statistical data collection. If you think that the use of this technology is unacceptable for you, in the browser settings you can always turn off the function of saving cookies. 

## 3\. Purpose of collect and use of information

3.1. We use your personal information solely for the purpose of providing our services and improving the work of the Site. In particular, the data received in electronic form is used for registering users, maintaining statistics, supporting the operation of services, improving the functionality of the Site. 

3.2. We can use the collected information to implement feedback from you. For example, if you left us comments through the Site, we will respond to them using your personal information. 

## 4\. Disclosure of information to third parties

4.1. The Administration and employees of the Site have confidentiality obligations, therefore they can’t transfer personal information of User to a third party without his consent, except for the situations described in paragraph 4.2. 

4.2. We may disclose your personal information if we receive an official request from law enforcement agencies or a court decision regarding information related to Users of the Site. If in accordance with the law we are required to provide personal data, but it isn’t forbidden to disclose the fact of receiving this request, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you about it. 

4.3. Please note that the information that you personally disclose in comments to a product or publication becomes public and can be read by other users. The Site is not responsible for the use of public information by third parties. 

4.4. Transfer of data to other countries. We can transfer some non-personal statistics outside the European Economic Area for processing by analytical services that provide data transmission protection that meets the requirements of the GDPR and that provide the same protection of the processed data as in Europe. 

## 5\. Security and protection of personal data

5.1. The Site Administration takes the necessary measures to protect your personal information from loss and unauthorized distribution and uses it solely within the confines of this Privacy Policy. Security is realized by means of network protection, using cryptographic methods of information protection, access control procedures, observance of the Privacy Policy. 

5.2. It is necessary to understand that all actions performed by the User who entered the Site under your profile will be considered to be committed personally by you. Therefore, in order to protect your account from unauthorized access, you must adhere to the following recommendations: 

  * always log out of your profile after completing the work with the Site, if other users have access to the computer;
  * always monitor access to your Telegram account, because an malefactor can access it and thus enter the Site on your behalf.

5.3. Data Retention Policy. 

User data is stored no longer than necessary for the purposes for which personal data was collected. 

## 6\. User rights

6.1. European Users have the right to request confirmation of the fact of processing their data, the place and purpose of processing, the categories of personal data being processed, to which third parties the personal data is disclosed, the period during which the data will be processed, and to clarify the source of receipt of personal data and require their correction. Moreover, the User has the right to demand the termination of processing of his data. 

6.2. The right to be forgotten. 

The user has the opportunity to delete his profile and all his information from the system by contacting the administration of the Site on the contact details given below. 

6.3. The right to data portability. 

This right is that the user has the right to request from the Site Administration an electronic copy of his personal data for transfer to another company. 

## 7\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

7.1. We reserve the right to periodically update this Privacy Policy or supplement it with new items. Such changes come into force from the date of publication of this document. 

7.2. We will notify Users of the Site about changes through push notifications or other pop-up notifications on the Site. However, we recommend that you review our Privacy Policy from time to time to see if there are any new rules for working with your personal information. 

7.3. Your continued use of the Site and our services demonstrates the agreement with the changes made to the Privacy Policy. 

## CONTACT US

If you have any inquiries or complaints, you may contact us: 

  * by email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
  * in writing: Golovinskoe shosse, 5, Moscow, Russia, 125212
  * by Telegram: [@turutiki](https://t.me/turutiki)
